好 欢迎回来
齐哥好
班农先生好
能听到声音吗
齐哥能听到声音吗
还没有开麦
可以听到我们的声音是吧
可能那边声音还没调好
那我们先让新加进来的几位嘉宾
新加进来的几位嘉宾做一下介绍吧
老班长
好 齐哥好 班农先生好 各位好
亲爱的战友们大家好
今天是一个特别特别值得纪念的日子
我们爆料革命
我们爆料革命四年多以来
还有很多日子都值得纪念
而1120无一事当中最重要的一个之一
所以说今天我们在这里隆重的来纪念这一天
来分享这一路以来爆料革命的一些感受
我非常荣幸 谢谢
好 曹根
好的 齐哥好 班农先生好
亲爱的战友们好 观众朋友们好
我非常荣幸参加1120这个节目
这是应该是第二次了
第一次的时候每一次的1120都印象非常深刻
这一次非常有幸能够参与进来 谢谢
好 唐萍
全球战友们好 齐哥好 班农先生好
今天很激动
我们的法治基金法治社会到现在成立已经三周年了
还记得三年前
我是一直激动的守在手机的APP前面
收看这个1120的新闻发布会
王健之死的新闻发布会
而且没想到同时听到了这个消息
就是成立法治基金法治社会
所以说三年过来了
我觉得星星之火可以燎原
之前我们是没有火
一直这个火种是2017年文贵先生出来
他点起了这个火种
然后到了18年的1120
真的就是我们形成了一个这么大的灭共的联盟
然后我们全球有那么多的战友
那么一直到今天三年以后
到今天这把火真的是越烧越旺了
可以燎原了
谢谢大家
谢谢
好 谢谢
威廉王
七哥好 班农先生好
所有的战友们大家好
今天非常的激动能参加1120的纪念日
然后1120对于我来说意义也是非常大
当时确实是特别的震撼
当七哥向全世界宣告黑夜已经来临
然后真的是首次警告了全世界的人
关于共产党的黑暗
所以我们在现在的财富增长的同时
一定不要忘了我们的初心
我们是因为什么被吸引到不老革命
我们到底是为了干什么来的
所以这个纪念日真的是非常非常重要
非常感谢
很高参加 谢谢
好 谢谢威廉王
那我们赵英杰
好 七哥好 班农先生好
全球的战友大家好
很高兴今天和大家见面
虽然我其实参加爆料革命我们比较晚
王健之死这些七哥当时三年前开始爆料的时候
我们还不知道怎么回事呢
所以今天第一次这个日子和大家团聚在一起
谢谢
好 海龙先生
好 全球的战友们
七哥 班农先生大家好
我是非常非常欣慰幸运的
接过了这个班农先生的这个法治基金的主席
我想这是真正为中国人民
为老百姓在全球的唯一的这个法治基金
这么一个基金来去为中国人 为中国老百姓
班农先生经常说的这句话深深的感动我
我知道他是从一个美国人 外国人的一个嘴里面说出来
老百姓这三个字是对我们中国人多大的认可
多么多么的有亲切的这种感受的
心心相惜的这种感觉感受
所以在这儿都是相信爆料革命新中国联邦法治基金
所有在七哥创造的这个平台上
我们会也一定能把中国共产党就像我们在宣言里说的一样
八九六这个这个2020六四的时候
消灭中共是正义的需要
好 谢谢
好 谢谢海龙先生
谢谢海龙先生
那我们也看到了这在所有的框当中
除了这个文威先生和班农先生以外
基本上都是目前的这个法治基金
或者法治社会的董事或者说认知
那在我们看到班农先生和文威先生
其实创建了这个法治基金法治社会
我相信我记得文威先生过去有讲过
就是法治基金法治社会
一定是在我们这个中国人手上
或者说咱们战友手上去更更好的用好这些每一分钱
用到这个灭共的事业上面去
我想今天文威先生和班农先生看到
今天的法治基金法治社会的运作和合法合规的在操作
我相信他们也会比更更放心
好的 那文威先生
好 这个
我刚刚跟班农刚离开以后
我们俩离开这个屋就真的是
来上洗手间控制就一直在开会
开会呢 刚才开完会我到了洗手间
我是蹲在马桶上啊
边大便边换上衣
然后擦完屁股及时提着鞋就穿出来了
然后就点雪茄
真的一秒钟时间没有
班农先生每次进洗手间那边人家喊
出来
所以说我们就赶快来开会
人家人走了我们俩就穿到这儿来了
进着屋之前点着着雪茄
你看他们很轻松
真的是在高校的工作
而且班农先生你说他
跟我这样的年龄的人
一起跟人家开会
他就这样子很不容易的
所以说今天法治基金的时候
当我们谈的是兄弟姐妹们记住
班农先生真的是
用共产党的话说
真的是傲尽了自己的心思
真的是多少个不名业
跟我们一起1120
还当时建立法治社会法治基金
这是我跟班农先生
在三年前亲身经历的
今天又是同一个时间
同样的就是还是这样的辛苦的
他是为了我们
班农先生没有在法治基金
法治社会拿一分钱
而这个时候他今天想到的
和昨天和三年前想到的
真的最多中国老百姓
他想的最多的老百姓
包括我们刚才谈到的很多话题
就你能感受到这个外国人
是真的假的对咱们中国人好
他一想到
一说要能解救中国老百姓
他的眼睛就放光了
我们要赶快吧
行动快行动
班农先生在美国
最早跟随我说的
action action
行动行动行动
我们真的是大家要爱班农
这是why we love you
even you change we don't love you
don't be changed
我说你变了牛肉
no beef
今天班农先生吃饭
我说我要给你拍下来
no time eating food
that's why
所以说今天我们是
今天午饭特别好吃
说实话我都没有
因为他的事都太大了
我们谈到了郝海东先生的安全
叶钊永女士的安全
我们谈到了未来新西兰需要我们的保护
我们谈到了澳大利亚
现在发生了一系列的事件
我们谈到了加拿大
现在我们知道了情报
会对华人什么样的威胁
我们谈到日本
什么样会对我们的威胁
包括在台湾香港
所有的都谈到这个问题
这都是非常非常非常重要
每时每刻都对我们很重要
我们要做一系列的决定
要不要做这个
要不要做那个
我们不可能什么都做到
但是我们要做出正确
这就是班农先生
他绝对是我们的master
大师姐
这是真的是
现在大家有什么要问班农的
请你们问吧
我们就先从那个老班长开始吧
老班长
老班长声音
好的
谢谢非常非常感谢班农先生
一路以来
跟我们爆料革命
坚定的站在一起
为我们法治基金的最初的创立
做出了最大最大的贡献
非常令人激动
作为一个美国人
作为一个政治家
影响世界的政治家
您对我们法治基金
这三年以来的工作
能不能跟我们
做一个非常非常简短的评价
它的意义是什么
谢谢班农先生
谁翻译
这边有翻译
声音单
我以为让我翻译
我的翻译
老班长说
谢谢班农先生
为我们站在一起
帮助我们建立法律和社会的基础
我们非常感谢您的努力和支持
在短短的时间内
您能够简短地说一下
您所做的工作
很简短地说
法律和社会的法律
在这三年来上做过
谢谢
我觉得最重要的工作
是跟威士罗社会合作
尽可能帮助我们
在中国被中共制之后
对武汉病毒
尽可能帮助我们
西方的数量,人们都被消失了,
有被革命的灭亡,
为何中国人民需要法律,
为何他们需要被法律管治。
记得3年前,
当这个开始时,
Miles和其他团队,
西方没有人有任何理由
关于那些千万人,
无论是高级电影明星,
或是政府人员,
或是老百姓,
被中国共产党消失了。
这几年来,
我认为这件事很惊人,
这件事是由国际法律组织做的,
国际法律组织,
在中国和香港和其他地方
都在帮助中国人,
对中共病毒的做法,
我认为国际法律的努力
在过去三年来,
我希望在这三年来,
就像我们在创立法律组织时期
所做的那三年来一样有效。
谢谢班农先生。
班农先生刚才说,
在过去三年中,
法治基金主要是以救人为主,
不管是从救人,
从中共大陆出来,
或者是给药,
主要的工作就是给西方传播真相,
就是给西方人解释,
为什么中国人会需要民主和法治,
不好意思,有点紧张,
法治和民主,
因为在三年前刚开始的时候,
其实没有西方人知道中国人在受苦,
没有人知道中国人在被消失,
所以过去的三年,
我们传播中共的真相,
真的是非常有力的一个力量。
好,谢谢。
草根,
可以用英语直接问。
好的,
我英语不好,我就用中文的。
班农先生好,
班农先生作为西方最高权力的,
美国总统的首席战略大师,
对我们中国人的支持,
对郭先生的支持,
可以说意义非凡,
一个西方最有影响力,最有远见著实的人,
而且是一个赢家。
班农先生之前帮助川普总统,
赢得总统,
现在我相信他也能帮助我们中国人获得胜利。
我有一个问题就是说,
班农先生在面对压力,
面对巨大的打击挫折的情况下,
还如何保持信心?
我相信这对未来我们中国人,
会非常有帮助。
谢谢。
谢谢草根小哥。
他说,
美国最有影响力的政治家,
或者西方国家,
你必须帮助川普,
赢得选举,
你必须帮助我们赢得我们的国家。
他的问题是,
你面对很多困难,
你如何克服它们?
你有什么建议,
或建议可以跟我们分享吗?
谢谢。
非常简单。
我来自美国的劳百姓,
我父母非常尊敬。
我父亲一百岁,
但他是一名电话公司的职员。
他们教导我,
保持战争的价值。
我们是英国人,
所以我们不会停止战争。
我认为,
无论是为了帮助川普,
为了帮助川普,
赢得第一次,
或是为了帮助他,
赢得第二次,
或是为了帮助中国人民,
赢得第一次,
他们都很困难,
但如果你们被父母侵犯,
如果你们被父母侵犯,
我们会把川普总统的总统帐号删除,
然后把总统帐号删除。
好,谢谢。
好,那我们下面唐萍。
我有两个问题要问。
一件事,
为了帮助川普,
为了帮助他,
赢得第一次,
或是为了帮助他,
在美国。
好。
班农先生说这个Tick Down的CCP这首歌
现在在美国全国是流行第一名的一首歌曲。
对。
还有我们的新歌,
H Coins To The Moon。
那个是我们的作品,
蛮漂亮的。
对。
应该很不错,我相信。
Miles唱歌很难,
没有H Coins,
没有Miles唱歌,
这是第一名的歌曲,
第二名的歌曲,
第三名的歌曲,
帮助我成为巨星。
没有Miles唱歌,
你们三个成为我的英雄。
非常感谢。
谢谢。
我有两个问题想问班农先生。
第一个问题就是
您看
真的是在这个早期
就是爆料革命的早期,
当郭先生一个人单枪匹马,
一个人抗议国的
这样的一个情况下,
当时我觉得
整个的海外的民运,
那个也是
就是很乱的,
都是乱象,
有很多的伪类,大白犬什么的。
当时是什么样的一个信念
支持你,就是坚定不移的
要去跟郭先生
在一起战斗,
然后才有了我们的
1120的这样的一个
在纽约的一个发布会。
当时你跟郭先生两个人
真的就是宣布
这个法治基金成立,
但是我们真的是欢欣鼓舞的,
所有的华人,
就是说有什么样的
这样的一个
勇气来支持你
来做这件事情,就是坚定不移的
支持文贵先生,
支持郭先生,跟他站在一起战斗。
那么你有没有想过
接下来,就是
当时有没有想过,接下来
会碰到很多很多的
构陷啊,污蔑啊,
就是很多的困难。
这是我第一个问题,然后第二个问题就是
您经常是把老百姓
中国的,中国人
就是挂在嘴边去,
那么您认为,中国人
是哪些方面
值得你这么义无反顾的
可以去,我相信你
真的是
在用你的生命,在为
中国人去争取这份民主
和自由的,所以这个是让
我们所有的战友啊,所有的华人
都特别感动的一件事情,
那么是什么力量去支持你的,
就这两个问题,谢谢。
好,谢谢小杨姐。
嗯,so in the beginning of the
movement when Miles was alone
fighting with the CCP, the
Chinese movements in the US was a
mess, so what was your motivation
to stand with Miles and
what drove you to support Miles?
Have you thought about the obstacles,
deformation and trouble?
Thank you.
Unlike anybody had come to the West,
Miles
talked about things
and warned the West
about
very sophisticated, the people
had come before, don't get me wrong,
were good people, but it was the Tiananmen Square
democracy movement and
other maybe lawyers
and human rights activists, and although it was very
moving, it didn't
and people
felt for the Chinese people, it didn't
strike a chord at the high power
levels. When Miles came
over to the West,
his first warning to the West in
quite shocked me, because
the level of detail and the level of
sophistication. Then when I saw
him take on H&A,
which at the time was the largest
financial company in the world, and
was supported by all of Wall Street,
Goldman Sachs, Merrill Lynch, Bank of
America, and he was attacked, attacked,
attacked, and said
that this was a money laundering
operation, an influencing
operation that had stolen everything from
the Chinese people and was laundering it
into the West. It resonated
with me as a very sophisticated analysis
of a company, and he
was taking on, not the little guys, he
was taking on the power structure,
not just in Beijing, in America,
and calling them out.
And when they tried
to shut him up,
he sued him, he used the
courts, the rule of law in America
to go after him, and guess
what, they all, they all
stopped, they all cratered, they all said, oh, excuse
me, you know, I don't want to go to court, I don't want
to go in a court of law.
And then Miles warned about Hong Kong,
and then he warned about the CCP
virus, and so everything
was not at a low level, it was a very high
level, and it just wasn't pointing
to Beijing, which all the
other Chinese dissents had always pointed to Beijing.
He pointed to
America and London
and Davos
and the banks and the
hedge funds and the corporations
that were in partnership with
the CCP. And I said,
this is extraordinary. His warning to the West
is right, because remember, it's one unified
system, and the reason that
the regime in Beijing exists
is because of
Wall Street and the corporations
and the political influence they've gotten by taking
the Lao Bai Jing money and funding it
to the West, and stealing it
for themselves, and making the
Western banks and investment banks and hedge
funds lots of money. So you
could see the whole system, and you could see he
was attacking the heart of the system.
That's courage, right, because
that's why his life is always, that's why they've been
under pressure, because he's speaking
what we say here is truth to power,
right, truth to power.
And I admired that, and I said
if this corrupt system's
going to come down, you have to
be in partnership with people
like that who are fearless,
who have courage, because
as Churchill told us, courage
is contagious,
and courage will embolden
other people, and that's what I've seen over the last couple
of years. Have you seen how far we've
come with the foundation
of the new federal state, and the
growth of the whistleblower
movement, and the
rule of law foundation, rule of society, just
in a few years. These are now
significant institutions that are
attack, attack, attack every day
with real information. Look at
G-News, GTV, Getter, all these
institutions. This is
institutionalizing a new China
with the new Chinese,
young Chinese, and that is very
powerful. So that's why I thought Miles
was, and I understood,
every bad guy in our country was trying
to get him extradited
back to Beijing. So I said
my mother,
my mom had a very good
saying when I was
a young boy, that you can tell the quality
of a man by
who his enemies are,
right? And I looked at Miles and I said
this guy's got all the right
enemies. He's hated
by all the right people,
right? All the super bad guys
here in America and in Beijing.
And so that's why it's
and I keep telling people,
I said just look at what Miles
said at the time he said it
and look what happened. And I
say this all the time. If America
and the West
had heeded his warning
when he first came here in 2017,
the world would be in a very different position.
You wouldn't have the global
chaos and anarchy of the CCP
virus, right? And who knows
what to come after that. We wouldn't be in trouble
in the South China Sea or in Taiwan,
right? The Uyghurs wouldn't be
the Uyghurs wouldn't be in
prison, right? So many of these
ills that the power structure
of the West has gone along with
and Davos has gone along
with and the World Economic Forum and the city
of London and Wall Street has all gone along
with. If we had just heeded
Miles Guo's warning in 2017,
the world would be a more peaceful,
prosperous
and healthy place.
Thank you, Mr.
Bannon.
Thank you, Mr. Bannon.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
Hold on, hold on. Hold on.
You lost three points.
Three points.
Sir Steve know me as
before in the Beijing
is the Pan-Gu Olympic 2008.
So you know
a lot about, you know,
Pan-Gu. So that's Pan-Gu
still in China. Only one
private developer,
real estate party in the Pan-Gu area
even now, right?
Yes.
You know we have capability.
This one, right? You know before
2008.
So secondly, you need
to know we are, we talk a lot
about the China history,
global history, you know,
also the American history
and the philosophy, right?
And the phrase, religion.
So that's hard to have, sphere to sphere.
Second, three, you never
forgot. You see Miles, you are
about the food, and the
quality, and the
direction, and Miles look at the
faces, handsome. That's the three
reasons. You forgot the point, Master.
Miles is just a blower of me now.
What's a blower?
Back in 2008
though, when I was at the
Olympics, Miles was super
high level. I was just, I was
la bai jing. Yeah, yeah, you're really low.
I was la bai jing.
No, impossible to get in
pangolin.
Top, top, top.
Global elite, global elite.
I'm
pretty wrong.
I need
all the clothes. Only you use
pangolin. Only you.
I guarantee.
Okay.
Okay,
okay,
然后刚才唐明杰的第二个问题呢
and have a great sense of humor right
and they understand how tough life is
but they they press on
so it's grit determination
belief and family values and tradition
honoring who came before you
right the family
and also the
the importance of knowledge and learning
right every Chinese family
I've met every young Chinese person
but how do I get
how do I do well in school
how do I go to the best schools
how do I learn
you can see this at G News and GTV
get all the companies
how do I learn my profession better
how do I get more skills
and the work ethic
you know you make
most of the times you have to send the young Chinese people home
right because this is going to work and work
and work and work and work
so it's that stick-to-it-iveness
it's that grit
it's that determination
you're making yourself better
that you're making future generations
you're providing a foundation for future generations
so Lao Bai Jing
look I come from the American version of Lao Bai Jing
we are my family is just the little guys
right all you know
80% 85% of my family
today the extended family
are blue collar workers
right laborers
you know craftsmen skilled craftsmen
but still Lao Bai Jing
but they have that same type of common quality
and family
and wanting to be left alone by the government
the government to tell them what to do
they don't want to tell them how many children they have
how to raise their children
how to educate their children
and so I think that those qualities
and those are the qualities
that are going to overthrow the Chinese Communist Party
because the Chinese Communist Party
is antithetical to all those values
they're all about money
and power and materialism
no faith
no spirituality
no caring about anybody
no grace
no gratitude
none of it
that's why three years ago today
remember what we put up shocked the world
we put the faces of all the people that disappeared
committed suicide
disappeared were in prison or had their assets stole
that's from a regime
who doesn't care about people
at all
and that's different than Lao Bai Jing
that's the values
of the traditional
Chinese society
that will eventually overthrow
the dictatorial cruelty
and evilness of the Chinese Communist Party
thank you Mr.Bannon
刚才班农先生说
之所以他
把他的全部的生命
都要献给咱们的爆料革命
是因为他看到中国人
他的决心毅力
他看到中国人的这种生活方式
还说了中国人也非常的幽默
知道生活有多苦
但是还是非常非常努力工作
不停地都在问我怎么样可以做得更好
我怎么样可以提高
而且每一个中国人都非常的勤劳
非常的坚定
能够让自己更好
让自己的未来也更好
班农先生也说他自己是美国的老百姓
他们家的85%的人到现在都是蓝领
是普通的工人
他们也有和我们中国老百姓一样的品质
对比西方华尔街的巨头和现在的政府
他们没有信仰没有感恩
也没有仁慈
所以就是因为咱们有中华最传统
最珍贵的这些品质
才让他能够一直帮助咱们爆料革命
谢谢
好嘞
感谢了
班农先生问得非常好
我再说一遍
在中国的国际关系
言语
宗教
文化
中国的中国社会
和美国的历史
这是最困难的
他们称之为
精神性
每天三个小时
在晚餐后
每天都会去Lady May 2
喝一杯咖啡
听中国音乐
每天
每天120天
这是非常重要的
史蒂夫·金班农对我的心情
120天
没有一天
没有一天你问我中国老百姓
你很关心
为什么
中国没有中华人民共和国
为什么这可以发生
为什么长期以来
没有人会改变政策
我说因为美国和西方世界
中国是一个很坏的男人
中国是一个很大的太空
和最大的团体
他们是中国的文化
他们是美国的文化
这是为什么我们分享了很多
国际的文化
宗教
文化
经济
技术
中国
CCP